{"QuestionsAndAnswers1":[
    {
        "Question":"Which of the following is a valid name?",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<_person>",
            "B":"<123person>",
            "C":"Both A and B",
            "D":"None of the above"
        },
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "Question":"From which tag does the descriptive list starts?",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<LL>",
            "B":"<DD>",
            "C":"<DL>",
            "D":"<DS>"
        },
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The body tag usually used after",
        "Options":{
            "A":"Title tag",
            "B":"HEAD tag",
            "C":"EM tag",
            "D":"FORM tag"
        },
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which tag creates a number/order list?",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<UL>",
            "B":"<OL>",
            "C":"<OT>",
            "D":"None of the above"
        },
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "Question":"HTML is a subset of",
        "Options":{
            "A":"SGMT",
            "B":"SGML",
            "C":"SGMD",
            "D":"None of these"
        },
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "Question":"<Base> tag is designed to appear only between",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<HEAD>",
            "B":"<TITLE>",
            "C":"<BODY>",
            "D":"<FORM>"
        },
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Markup tags tell the web browser",
        "Options":{
            "A":"How to organise the page",
            "B":"How to display the page",
            "C":"How to display message box on page",
            "D":"None of the above"
        },
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Web pages starts with which of the following tag?",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<Body>",
            "B":"<Title>",
            "C":"<HTML>",
            "D":"<FORM>"
        },
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "Question":"HTML stands for?",
        "Options":{
            "A":"Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "B":"High Text Markup Language",
            "C":"Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
            "D":"None of the above"
        },
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Correct HTML tag for the largest heading is",
        "Options":{
            "A":"<head>",
            "B":"<h6>",
            "C":"<heading>",
            "D":"<h1>"
        },
        "Answer":"D"
    }
]}